<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Colab on vigliensoni</title><link>https://vigliensoni.com/tags/colab/</link><description>Recent content in Colab on vigliensoni</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 19:41:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vigliensoni.com/tags/colab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clastic music web application</title><link>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/33-clastic-music-webapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/33-clastic-music-webapp/</guid><description>The Clastic Music web app is an interactive application where images are rendered in real time and react to music and human input. It was conceived and developed by Eduardo Pérez Infante and Gabriel Vigliensoni.
Clastic music web application interface Some time ago, Eduardo and I were working on an A/V presentation for a show at Mutek Montréal. We didn&amp;rsquo;t know at the moment, but that show turn up to be the Clastic Music record.</description></item><item><title>Scintillation</title><link>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/32-scintillation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 19:41:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/32-scintillation/</guid><description>Scintillation is the result of a first time collaboration between CMD and vigliensoni. It explores our joint desires for fast-paced rhythms, propulsive basslines, and affective melodies.
This is our contribution to the Dance Across Borders Vol. 3 compilation, the most recent edition of this series raising funds for the human rights organization Solidarity Across Borders (www.solidarityacrossborders.org)— a non-profit that works to protect human rights.
Buy the full album on Bandcamp</description></item><item><title>Real-time control of neural audio synthesis | Ella</title><link>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/40-neural-audio-ella/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/40-neural-audio-ella/</guid><description>Street improvisation with neural audio synthesis models. In the video I am improvising with sound artist dedosmuertos, in La Villette, Paris. I am interacting in real time with the latent space representation of several models trained on raw audio using the RAVE neural network architecture (Caillon and Esling, 2021). To interact with the latent space, I am using a Gametrak controller. By means of Wekinator (Fiebrink and Cook, 2009), an application for supervised, interactive machine learning, I&amp;rsquo;m mapping the performance space to the latent space representation of the model.</description></item><item><title>Ñe'ê: Earwitnessing hidden stories from the South</title><link>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/41-earwitnessing-hidden-stories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/41-earwitnessing-hidden-stories/</guid><description>Project conceived and developed by Maar Colasso and Gabriel Vigliensoni.
Check the generative radio portal site.
Ñe&amp;rsquo;ê: Earwitnessing hidden stories from the South is a generative radio project and sound performance that seeks to unveil stories and historical events from the Latin-American South on the idea of disappearance and memory. By placing together sound objects from distant geographies, times, and cultures in a non-binding way—therefore allowing the interaction of their contexts, memories, and temporal densities—this project aims at enabling the audience to reflect and provide meaning to these events.</description></item><item><title>Ola de Calor</title><link>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/11-ola-de-calor/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/11-ola-de-calor/</guid><description>Letra y música por Ignacio Redard y Gabriel Vigliensoni.
Producida por Ignacio Redard, Gabriel Vigliensoni y Lucy C.
Mezclada por Barry Sage en Estudio Home (CL).
Masterizada por Bob Macc en Subvert Central Mastering (UK).
Portada por Buena Estudio.
Ola de Calor es distribuído por Santiago Récords. Released October 22, 2021.
MusicBrainz | Discogs</description></item><item><title>Tragatierra</title><link>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/10-tragatierra/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 20:22:08 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://vigliensoni.com/portfolio/10-tragatierra/</guid><description>Letra y música por Gabriel Vigliensoni e Ignacio Redard.
Producida por Gabriel Vigliensoni e Ignacio Redard.
Voces adicionales por Vito.
Mezclada por Barry Sage en Estudio Home (CL).
Masterizada por Bob Macc en Subvert Central Mastering (UK).
Portada por Buena Estudio
Tragatierra es distribuído por Santiago Récords. Released September 3, 2021.
MusicBrainz | Discogs</description></item></channel></rss>